<sburb description="sixth room">

<dependencies>
	<dependency>chars/karkat.xml</dependency>
  <dependency>chars/terezi.xml</dependency>
</dependencies>

<assets>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_0_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_0_0.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_0_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_0_1.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_0_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_2_1.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_1_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_1_0.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_1_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_1_1.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_1_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_2_1.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_2_0' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_2_0.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_2_1' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_2_1.png</asset>
<asset name='sixthRoomBG_2_2' type='graphic'>backgrounds/slices/sixthRoomBG_2_1.png</asset>
	<asset name='sixthRoomMap' type='graphic'>backgrounds/sixthRoomMap.png</asset>

  <asset name='gamzeeSheet' type='graphic'>objects/gamzee.png</asset>
  <asset name='tereziSit' type='graphic'>objects/terezi_sit.png</asset>
  <asset name='gamzee_idle' type='graphic'>dialogs/gamzee/gamzee_idle.png</asset>
  <asset name='snooze' type='graphic'>objects/snooze.png</asset>

</assets>

<hud>
  <dialogsprites>
    <animation name='gamzee_idle' sheet='gamzee_idle' x='-220' y='-420'/>
  </dialogsprites>
</hud>

<character class='karkat' x='792' y='638'>
      <action sprite='dave' command='talk' name='Talk to Karkat.'>
        <args>
        @karkat_talk KARKAT: OK, THIS IS JUST FUCKING STUPID NOW.
        @dave_idle DAVE: what
        @karkat_talk KARKAT: I'M ASLEEP, BUT I GUESS THE METEOR IS PHYSICALLY PASSING THROUGH THE BUBBLE I'M DREAMING IN?
        @karkat_talk KARKAT: AND NOW MY "DREAM PHANTOM", OR WHATEVER THE FUCK YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO CALL THIS VERSION OF YOURSELF, IS ACTUALLY IN THE SAME PHYSICAL LOCATION AS MY SLEEPING BODY.
        @karkat_yell KARKAT: I'VE JUST BEEN STANDING HERE WATCHING MYSELF SLEEP ON THE HORN PILE. IT'S OFFICIAL. WE'VE BREACHED A CRITICAL THRESHOLD OF BULGE NUMBING IDIOCY. 
        @dave_huh DAVE: huh
        @karkat_yell KARKAT: WHAT DO WE EVEN CALL THIS DREAMING INSTANCE OF OURSELVES? IT CAN'T BE "DREAM SELF" BECAUSE THAT'S ALREADY A THING. AS IN THE VERSION OF YOURSELF ON DERSE OR PROSPIT.
        @karkat_yell KARKAT: BUT THAT WAS MORE LIKE A PHYSICAL, REAL SELF, THAT JUST HAPPENED TO SERVE AS A BACKUP LIFE. THIS IS SOMETHING TOTALLY DIFFERENT, LIKE A WEIRD HOLOGRAM.
        @karkat_what KARKAT: HEY, AM I TANGIBLE TO YOU?
        @dave_huh DAVE: uh
        @karkat_idle KARKAT: TOUCH ME.
        @dave_huh DAVE: what
        @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: JUST GIVE ME A LITTLE POKE.
        @dave_mad DAVE: no
        @karkat_talk KARKAT: DON'T BE LIKE THAT, JUST MAN UP AND TOUCH ME. MAYBE JUST BRUSH MY CHEEK GENTLY WITH THE BACK OF YOUR HAND. SOMETHING UNAMBIGUOUSLY PLATONIC LIKE THAT.
        @dave_mad DAVE: no fuck you
        @dave_madtalk DAVE: im not caressing your dream hologram
        @karkat_facepalm KARKAT: YOU HAVE A REALLY TRAGICALLY UNDER-INQUISITIVE MIND, DAVE. THIS IS FOR SCIENCE. IF SCIENCE WAS UP TO YOU, HUMANITY NEVER WOULD HAVE COME ANYWHERE CLOSE TO RISING TO THE LEVEL OF PATHETIC INFERIORITY IT WAS BARELY ABLE TO ACHIEVE AS IT WAS.
        @dave_talk DAVE: you look really tired man
        @dave_talk DAVE: your sleep phantom should curl up with your napping meat torso in the horn pile and try to score some shuteye
        @karkat_shout KARKAT: YEAH, WELL MAYBE I'LL DO JUST THAT, ASSHOLE!
        @dave_idle DAVE: ok
        @dave_idle DAVE: hop to it
        @karkat_sullen KARKAT: NO. NOT WHILE YOU'RE WATCHING.
        @dave_idle DAVE: man
        @dave_talk DAVE: our conversations can be so embarrassing
        @dave_talk DAVE: im so glad we manage to have most of them in private
        @karkat_eyeroll1 KARKAT: YEAH
        @karkat_eyeroll2 KARKAT: ME TOO
        <!--  -->
        </args>
      </action>
    </character>

   <sprite name='gamzee' x='422' y='624' width='40' height='24' collidable='true' depthing='1'>
      <animation sheet='gamzeeSheet' x='-30' y='-90'/>
      <action sprite='rose' command='talk' name='Parle à Gamzee.'>
            <args>
            @rose_talk ROSE: Tu ferais mieux de ne pas laisser Kanaya te voir dans les alentours.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Elle te déteste toujours, tu sais.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Et pas dans “ce sens”. Je pense qu’elle voudrait vraiment te tuer.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: ouais, je sais deja toutes ces putain de choses.
            @rose_concern ROSE: Je me demandais, cela ne rend pas les choses confuses ? D’essayer de faire la différence entre les sentiments platoniques, les malveillantes intentions et les signes d’une romance noire ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: NON.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: comme si j’allais laisser a cette salope lumineuse et a sa tronconneuse ne serait-ce qu’une place dans ma vie et mes quadrants.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: EN PLUS J’AI DEJA UN AUTRE FILS DE PUTE DANS MON QUADRANT NOIR.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: j’ai flirte avec quelqu’un depuis la putain d’obscurite. c’est devenu plutot sale entre nous. on a fait la putain d'experience de ce putain de miracle appele l’amour-haine. 
            @rose_concern ROSE: Attends, vraiment ?
            @rose_annoyed ROSE: Qui ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: :o)
            @rose_idle ROSE: Karkat ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: non.
            @rose_laugh ROSE: Dave ??
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: NON.
            @rose_sad ROSE: Pas... le Maire ???
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: non.
            @rose_concern ROSE: Attends...
            @rose_concern ROSE: Terezi ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: HONK.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Es-tu sérieux ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: est-ce que j’ai l’air de putain de blaguer avec les fils de pute ?
            @rose_idle ROSE: Je...
            @rose_annoyedtalk ROSE: Je n’arrive même pas à analyser cette relation comme étant réellement existante.
            @rose_annoyed ROSE: Comment...
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: C’EST SIMPLE. 
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: fils de pute.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: LA RAISON DE CETTE HAINE DANS LAQUELLE ELLE S’ENFONCE EST PLUTOT LOGIQUE, QUAND ON VOIT LE PUTAIN DE CONNARD DE CLOWN QUE JE SUIS.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: mais elle ne me hait pas au point de vouloir me tuer. :o)
            @rose_talk ROSE: Je dois dire que c’est là une ahurissante révélation.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Ça change la donne.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: HEY.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: s’il te plait va pas ébruiter tout ça.
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: SI KARKAT L’APPRENAIT...
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: il voudrait vraiment me tuer. :o(
            @rose_talk ROSE: Oui, je comprends le dilemme dans lequel tu te trouves.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Vos dynamiques sociales commencent à devenir réellement compliquées à partir du moment où vous remplissez vos quadrants, n’est-ce pas ?
            @gamzee_idle GAMZEE: PUTAIN, OUAIS, C’EST PUTAIN DE CA.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Ne t’en fais pas, ton secret est en sécurité avec moi.
            @rose_talk ROSE: Allez, psss. Maintenant retourne dans le système de ventilation avant que quelqu’un ne te voit
            <!--  -->
            </args>
      </action>
    </sprite>

    <sprite name='terezi' x='422' y='624' width='40' height='24' collidable='true' depthing='1'>
      <animation sheet='tereziSit' x='-30' y='-90'/>
      <action command='talk' name="C’est Terezi !" sprite='damara'>
          <args>
          @terezi_idle TEREZI: H3Y D4MZ !!!!
          @terezi_idle TEREZI: S1 TU T’4PPROCH3S D3 LU1, J3 T3 BUT3 !
          @damara_fu2 DAMARA:
          <!--  -->
          </args>
      </action>
    </sprite>

<rooms>
  <room name='sixthRoom' walkableMap='sixthRoomMap' mapScale='2'>
  	<triggers>

  		<trigger>
  			<args>inBox2,kanaya,751,998,503,900</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>rooms/thirdRoom.xml,thirdRoom,1668,378</action>
  		</trigger>

      <trigger>
        <args>inBox2,dave,751,998,503,900</args>
        <action command='removeSprite'>
          <args>karkat,sixthRoom</args>
          <action command='changeRoomRemote'>rooms/thirdRoom.xml,thirdRoom,1668,378</action>
        </action>
      </trigger>

      <trigger>
        <args>inBox2,rose,751,998,503,900</args>
        <action command='removeSprite'>
          <args>gamzee,sixthRoom</args>
          <action command='changeRoomRemote'>rooms/thirdRoom.xml,thirdRoom,1668,378</action>
        </action>
      </trigger>

      <trigger>
        <args>inBox2,damara,751,998,503,900</args>
        <action command='removeSprite'>
          <args>terezi,sixthRoom</args>
          <action command='changeRoomRemote'>rooms/thirdRoom.xml,thirdRoom,1668,378</action>
        </action>
      </trigger>

  	</triggers>

    

    <sprite name='snooze' x='570' y='450' >
      <animation sheet='snooze' length='4' frameInterval='10'/>
    </sprite>

    <sprite name='sleepKat' x='602' y='589' width='224' height='100'>
      <action sprite='kanaya' command='talk' name='Examine snoozing Karkat.'>
            <args>
            @meenah_idle MEENAH: !!!!!
            @! Hey, it's your newly recruited Grand Threshecutioner! Looks like he hasn't woken up from the same nap he was having last time you talked to him. The guy must have been really tired.
            @! Why's he sleeping in this massive pile of horns? That can't be too comfortable. Maybe you should wake him up. Then as long as he's awake, might as well see if he's ready to pack his bags and head off to war.
            @! Hold on. Maryam is eying you suspiciously. She isn't on to your plan, is she? How could she know? This girl is really cramping your style. You'd try to shake her loose, but as a rainbow drinker she seems to have an absolutely insane fastness attribute.
            @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Whatever Youre Thinking Dont Even Try It
            @meenah_wut MEENAH: what!!!
            @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: wasnt thinkin nofin
            @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Lets Keep Moving
            <!--  -->
            </args>
      </action>
      <action sprite='rose' command='talk' name='Examine snoozing Karkat.'>
            <args>
            @! "ZZZZZZZZZZZZZ," Karkat said from atop the towering heap of hilarious clown accessories.
            <!--  -->
            </args>
      </action>
      <action sprite='dave' command='talk' name='Examine snoozing Karkat.'>
            <args>
            @! So many horns. You've always wondered what the elusive juggalo troll even needs with so many horns? You think he may have some sort of problem. Also what is with trolls and their weird tendency to be found sleeping in horn piles? You can't even imagine a less comfortable place to nap. There are some things you will never understand.
            <!--  -->
            </args>
      </action>
      <action sprite='damara' command='talk' name='What have we here?'>
            <args>
            @damara_smilemean DAMARA: ..............
            <!--  -->
            </args>
      </action>
    </sprite>

    
  	
  	<sprite name='sixthRoomBG'>
  		<animation sheet='sixthRoomBG' sliced='true' colSize='500' rowSize='500' numCols='3' numRows='3'/>
  	</sprite>

  </room> 
</rooms>

</sburb>
