<sburb>
    <classes>
    	<action class='horussTalk1' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Talk to Horuss.'>
      <args>
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Your Harness... I mean Hayness. Highness I mean.
      @horuss_bashful:#Sh*ot!#I-mean-Hayness!#Whew. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; F*DDLEST*%25. Please pardon my utterly e%25ecrable language, and unforgivable stammering, your Horseness.
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I am a bale of nerves in your royal presence, and it has been so long. 
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And when I am so spooked, you must know how that causes me to even more firmly identify with the majestic hoofbeast.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: hey uh
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: horuss what...
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: what the fuck is that thing youre prefixing all your talkin with
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh, this? What, you don't recognize it?
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: no and its weirding me out
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Why, it is my smiling face, you s*lly, utterly superior person, you. Goggles and all. Can't you see?
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: i
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: guess??
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: its disturbin as heck to me for whatever reason
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; The last thing I desire is to disconcert our prodigal empress.
      @horuss_smiletalk:#I've-been-cutting-back-on-the-horse-puns-too,-as-you-can-see. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I just thought I would try smiling permanently and uncompromisingly, rather than resnorting to all those disgruntled e%25pressions I usually trot out.
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: why the eff would you want to do that
      @horuss_idle:#8=3 HORUSS: 8=D &lt; It was on Meulin's suggestion, actually.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: huh??
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh, I guess you must not have herd. She and I have developed quite a STRONG and stable moirallegiance recently.
      @meenah_idle:#disclamer:#less-impressed-than-i-sound MEENAH: daaaang
      @meenah_talk:#cats+horse#ftw MEENAH: that matchup makes no glubbin sense dude
      @horuss_laugh:#If-you're-going-to-go#Go-out-with-a-smile#8=D HORUSS: 8=D &lt; E%25actly. Whoof would have thought? If you a%25ed me before we all died whether I would consider romantically pairing with a r*d*culous midb100d, let alone Ms. Leijon of all people, I'd probably have died regardless, due to laughter-induced asphy%25iation.
      @horuss_smiletalk:#Dancestors#Or-shall-I-say#Dressagecestors? HORUSS: 8=D &lt; But do you know what it was that finally cleared the sweat steam-induced fog from my goggles? It was meeting our post-scratch counterparts. 
      @horuss_smiletalk:#Which-naturally-I-would-drain-right-away-through-the-custom-sweat-valves HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Seeing our corresponding young Alternians, why it threatened to produce a tear-induced f100d on the inside of my goggles.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Their relationship in spite of the STRONG class disparity I found to be so moving, so pure. It made me reconsider my perspective on Meulin entirely, who horsenestly I'd hardly ever given a second thought.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; It's funny, don't you think? How our young ancestors took to a completely different social configuration, making for some rather odd pairings, both platonic and otherwise. A whole host of counterintuitive minglings, up and down the hemospectrum with no regard for class compatibility. And yet it all seems to make a strange amount of sense. Neigh, I might go as far as saying it's all oddly rather...
      @horuss_sweat_bashful2 HORUSS: 8=D &lt; T*tillating? Or no, perhaps what I mean is some of their Alternian indiscretions feel a bit, I don't know...
      @horuss_oops HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Naughty?
      @horuss_crossed:#My-mouth-is-quite-the-l*ad-g*per-today. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh ph**ey, that's not what I mean either. (Pardon my p*ttymouth.) Now you'll probably mistake me for some kind of r*scally deviant.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: man why yall still act like you give a heap of manure about dating down on the spectrum
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you and nitram been a thing for how long now
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Yes, but no one was supposed to know about that!
      @horuss_sweat_bashful2:#Though-I-have-literally-smithed-such-items-before,-pun-notwithstanding. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; That was always to be my own private, um, e%25ploration. I had no intention of creating such a stirrup. 
      @horuss_sweat_talk:#A-spur-of-the-moment-affair,-really. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; It was only to be a very private, fleeting dalliance with a BUOY, but the whole thing became so quickly scandalized. 
      @horuss_crossed HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And soon others were whisked into it such as you and the vengeful rust b100d, and... well, imagine my embarrassment. Trust me, the last thing I wanted was for royalty such as yourself to know I was pursuing forbidden b100d. To be caught with my hoof in the chocolate jar, so to nicker.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: ill
      @horuss_idle2talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And I suppose I would have clopped my hands of the matter after the big k*rfuffle, but...
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I guess I didn't e%25pect to fall in love.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: 
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; It's true. I am not ashamed to say it. I fell mane over hooves. Phantom snout over phantom hind quarters. He...
      @horuss_bashful:#With-but-a-roguish-glance. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; He stole my breath away.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: wow life story alert do not care
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; My apologies, your E%25cellency.
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: just tell me why paling up with meu means you have to make that terrible face now
      @horuss_smiletalk:#Such-as#All-times. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; She's taught me to get in touch with my anger. Through a moderately discernible series of enthusiastic mimes, she has made it clear that it is much healthier to crush all negative emotions beneath a stampede of positivity, and to always be cheerful and upbeat no matter what, even if projecting that facade is at times physically painful.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: that is some shitsauce advice and you should give it up homes
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Um, yes. Very well.
      @horuss_mad HORUSS: (;≧Д≦) &lt; Is this better?
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: much
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='horussTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Ask Horuss to join.'>
      <args>
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Respectfully, your Superlative Magnificency, I do not think that would be advisable.
      @meenah_creepy:#HORSE-PUN#DIS-GIRL#ON-FIYA MEENAH: whoa shocker of the centaury
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Of course, I will if you order me to without hesitation. But lately I've been attempting to canter down a trail of nonviolence.
      @horuss_smiletalk:#Soon-I-may-even-be-able-to-say-STRENGTH-without-shouting. HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I've been saddled for so long with anger and hostility, and now my focus is on solving problems in ways that do not involve confrontation or physical STRENGTH.
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Technology can solve so many problems, for instance. Do you have any idea how much energy is stored in sweat which may be released through its steam?
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Have you any clue as to the MIGHT of a quadrupedal automaton powered by raging currents of steam coursing through its e%25quisite horizontal torso, and finally jetting through a perfect pair of metal nostrils? I could build as many as you like, my Empress.
      @meenah_talk:#unless-you-build-those-suckas-out-of-gold MEENAH: um no think i will pass on taking an army of snorting horsebots with me
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: so thats all you do is build stupid shit that runs on your sweat now?
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: cause i could really use a guy with muscle
      @meenah_creepytalk:#kinda-hot-actually MEENAH: i dunno if you seen this skull dude but he is RIPP-ED
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh no, that's far from my only preoccupation. I have also taken some time to perfect the art of humor.
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Would you like to hear a joke?
      @meenah_annoyed:#fine MEENAH: oh noes...
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; A horse trots into a thirst shanty. His muscular shoulders slouched, his noble head hanging low.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; The dairyjerk observes that the great beast is clearly despondent, and asks:
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=========D &lt; Why the long face?
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: euurergh
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: zahhak god damn it i am royally orderin you to stop doing that face forever
      @horuss_idle2 HORUSS: 8=o &lt; At once, my lady.
      @horuss_sadtalk HORUSS: 8o &lt; My formerly perky visage withdraws, while my fully erect posture shrivels at your regal disapproval.
      @horuss_idle2talk HORUSS: (ಠ益ಠ;) &lt; I shall henceforth emote in my customary manner, as such.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: respect
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


<action class='horussTalk3' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Be Horuss.'>
      <args>
      @horuss_idle2talk HORUSS: ᕦ(ò д óˇ)ᕤ &lt; Bring me a horse, and I am yours forever.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='horussTalk4' sprite='rufioh' command='talk' name='Parle à Horuss.'>
      <args>
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: yo yo, horuss mon gangster, ça gaze ?
      @rufioh_talk:#en-vra1-ça-fa1t-plutôt-mal \nRUFIOH: est-ce que je peux avo1r un noble check de la part de mon pote ? hé, oua1s… comme ça… p*ta1n oua1s
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: bref, j’ava1s prévu de te parler de quelque chose... quelque chose… euh d’assez 1mportant.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: à propos de nous et du futur tout ça tout ça… tu as une m1nute ?
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: ok, cool. donc… b*rdel… par où je commence...
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: tu sa1s qu’on a eu que des bons moments ensemble… c’éta1t gén1al.
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: bon, y’a peut-être pas eu que des bons moments… toutes ces conner1es éta1ent r1squées au début… avec mon ex tarée… oua1s. là n’est pas la quest1on.
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: souv1ens-to1 de comment tu éta1s… avant que tu ne t’1ntéresses à mo1 de cette façon… mec tu croya1s que je cra1gna1s ! haha, juste un autre serfsang pas d1gne de ton temps.
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: t’éta1s tellement énervé contre les gens comme mo1 et damara… tellement en colère, bordel. c’éta1t fl1ppant… et damara… avant elle éta1t gent1lle au poss1ble… je sa1s pas ce qu1 s’est passé. tu parles d’un changement de personnal1té… pour vous deux...
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: ma1s après pour je ne sa1s quelle ra1son… je suppose que tu voula1s commun1quer avec mo1 ? je veux d1re… en secret, je sa1s. tu ne voula1s pas être réprouvé de ton club noblesang CIP, j’a1 toujours p1gé ça. je comprena1s, tu vo1s ?
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: tu es donc venu dans ma forêt… sans jama1s r1en d1re à personne… on a tra1né ensemble. ça compta1t beaucoup pour mo1. je veux que tu le saches.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: les gens ont toujours eu des 1dées complètement folles à mon propos. comme quo1 j’éta1s ce brave aventur1er occupé à être badass et tout dans sa forêt. les gens ont genre … 1ls ont toujours voulu être avec mo1, ou… peut-être voula1ent-1ls ÊTRE mo1 ? c’éta1t complètement taré… même damara quand on sorta1t ensemble ne me comprena1t pas vra1ment, je pense… elle me metta1t sur ce p1édestal, genre, avant qu’elle pète un câble.
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: ma1s tu m’as vu pour ce que j’éta1s. ce qu1 veut d1re… un gars 1mparfa1t.
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: genre, je n’éta1s pas sûr de mo1, et tu as vu ça… du coup tu m’as réellement a1dé.
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: quand on éta1t dans les bo1s ensemble, tu m’as appr1s à me battre… appr1s à voler… appr1s à me vanter !
      @rufioh_laugh \nRUFIOH: Bon, pas l1ttéralement. je veux d1re… je sava1s comment fa1re ces choses-là. je sava1s théoriquement comment battre des a1les et voler dans le c1el. je sava1s comment d1re “bangarang” a vo1x haute s1 je le voula1s vra1ment… ma1s le truc est là. j’ava1s peur ! j’ava1s peur de voler et de tomber… j’ava1s peur de me battre et d’échouer… et j’ava1s peur de me vanter et… de ressembler à un p*ta1n d’1d1ot je suppose ! mdr...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: tu m’as a1dé à ne pas avo1r peur, ou être embarrassé par mo1-même peut-être… tu m’as juste a1dé à être mo1-même. du genre… juste être ok avec le fa1t de ne pas être parfa1t, de ne pas devenir ce que les gens pensent que je devra1s être.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: peut-être que ce n’est que de la nostalg1e… 1l y ava1t quelque chose de me1lleur autrefo1s… juste to1 et mo1 se relaxant dans la forêt. mais après on est entré dans le jeu.
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: et pour je ne sa1s quelle ra1son... je ne sa1s toujours pas pourquo1… damara a commencé à deven1r un peu plus folle chaque jour… devenant de plus en plus jalouse quand elle sava1t qu’on tra1na1t ensemble...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: et ensu1te elle a découvert que c’éta1t plus que juste tra1ner ensemble… et je suppose que le reste c’est de l’h1sto1re anc1enne.
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: et bla bla bla… ensu1te on est tous morts… et on a été ensemble depu1s. tout ce temps en fantômes...
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: ce qui fa1t… beaucoup de temps, tu sa1s ?
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: et je sera1s toujours reconna1ssant pour ce que nous avons vécu ensemble… ma1s… je suppose que les gens changent.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: même en tant que fantômes, 1ls changent, s1 tu leur la1sses suf1samment de temps… 1ls commencent à voulo1r d’autres choses
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: oh mec ! je m’y prends mal… je parle beaucoup trop ma1s pas de ce que je veux d1re… m*rde, haha.
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: je devra1s ut1l1ser la bravoure que tu m’as fa1s comprendre que j’ava1s depu1s toujours, et juste le d1re...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: je cro1s qu’on devra1t se séparer
      @rufioh_sad:#... \nRUFIOH: ...
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: euh...
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH:  ça va, poto ?
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh ! Je suis désolé, qu’est-ce que tu disais ?
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Mes valves auditives étaient remplies de sueur, je n’ai pas compris le trois-quart de ce que tu as dis.
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: ...
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Hey, pourquoi ne participerait-on pas plus tard à une activité conviviale ensemble, en tant que partenaires romantiques de l’au-delà ? Nous pourrions jouer à un de ces jeux de carte étrangers que tu 100bles apprécier. Comment ça s’appelait déjà ? Fiddlespoon ?
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: euh. oua1s… on peut fa1re ça...je suppose. ça a l’a1r… euh. génial.
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Je sais que je ne suis pas le meilleur partenaire pour partager tes intérêts e%otiques et quelque peu enfantins, mais je vais faire de mon mieux pour les comprendre et les apprécier avec toi. La chose la plus importante c’est que l’on passe du temps ensemble et que l’on maintienne une relation FORTE.
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: ...
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: bangarang.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='horussTalk5' sprite='damara' command='talk' name='Parle à Horuss.'>
      <args>
      @damara_meantalk DAMARA: これ以上のゲームはありません。馬男。今私をファック。
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; E%cuse-moi ?
      @damara_meantalk DAMARA: FICHEVLLOまたがっ私を曲げる。あなたは私がハードファック。CHEVALINスタイル。
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Ho ! Je vois que tu t’intéresses à ce beau, bien que minuscule, étalon qu’on l’on m’a offert plus tôt.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; N’est-ce pas merveilleux ? Je lui donnerai de nombreuses pommes et il sera FORT en grandi100.
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMARA: 私にリンゴを養う。その後、私の髪をつかむ。あなたはチャンピオンのように私に乗るだろう。
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Je ne… Faire quoi avec tes cornes ? Chevaucher quoi e%actement ?
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: のバケツを埋めることができます。その後、内容がスプラッシュ。私の体の上にすべての。次に干し草の山に私を投げる。
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Tu veu% que je… quelque chose à voir avec… de la paille ? Hm. 
      @damara_talk DAMARA: 私はあなたのホーンを吸うことができます。同時に、あなたは私のお尻を平手打ち。リズミカルにそれを行う。また。いななく。
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Tu veu% que je fasse… quoi de manière rythmé ? En faisant quel bruit animalier ?
      @damara_talk DAMARA: 私のすべての反復をファック。性的エクスタシーを体験する私たちのすべてを引き起こす。私たちは一斉にオーガズムましょう。
      @horuss_sweat_bashful2 HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Faire quoi avec… attends… toutes les toi e%istantes ? Est-ce que ça ne fait pas beaucoup de Damaras, peu importe l’activité que tu essayes de décrire ? 
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: 清潔なタオルで私を包んでください。私は農場の動物のようにうめき声をしなければならない。
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMARA: 私の足の間に腹立たしそうに鼻を鳴らす。私は殺された子羊のように悲鳴を上げるでしょう。
      @damara_fiendish DAMARA: 私たちは一緒に私たちのお尻を持ってみましょう。共通のオーガズムに参加。すべての終わりでは、私たちを取り囲んでいる。
      @horuss_crossed HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Essayer de décoder tes parole est assez stre100, tu sais.
      @horuss_crossed2 HORUSS: 8=D &lt; À chaque fois que je te parle, mon système est tout agité. 
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Je commence à re100tir une communication avec une ancienne âme d’Alternasie, et je suis sur le point de te comprendre. Mais tout disparaît aussi rapidement que c’est arrivé, et je suis laissé là avec rien d’autre qu’une accablante e%périence de transpiration. 
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Mais ce n’est pas comme si je m'attendais à ce qu’une basse sang de rouille célibataire comme toi comprenne. 
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: もっと私を低下させる。私はほとんどそこにいる。
      @damara_fu4 DAMARA: フリーク。
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
  	</classes>
</sburb>
