<sburb>
    <classes>
  		<action class='rufiohTalk1' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Parle à Rufioh.'>
	      <args>
	      @meenah_idle MEENAH: yo nitram
	      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: oh, salut poupée... t’éta1s part1e pendant vachement longtemps... 
	      @rufioh_happytalk: je-croya1s-que-tu-alla1s-faire-éclore-un-f1duspawn-avec-ce-truc-pour-être-honnête…  \nRUFIOH: cool de te revoir, cependant... yo, cette combine avec la bombe que tu nous as sort1e c’était de la fol1e p*ta1n.
	      @meenah_happy MEENAH: ctai pas ghareng chose
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: te sous-est1mes pas... je pense pas que j’aurais pu fa1re ça. t’es plutot gangsta, pe1xes.
	      @meenah_idle MEENAH: oui je sais
	      @meenah_talk:#jai-des-questions MEENAH: hey et si on arretait  de parler da quel point je suis badass une minute et quon parlait de toi
	      @rufioh_idle \nRUFIOH: vas-y, poupée...
	      @meenah_idle MEENAH: ces ailes
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: tu as eclot avec hein
	      @meenah_idle:#quand-tu-as-atteint-ta-puperte?? MEENAH: ou tu les as pupatees
	      @rufioh_laugh:#un-vocabulaire-genre...#tu-sais...#de-mots-normaux \nRUFIOH: ha, oua1s c’est ça… je su1s un “m*tant”... ne dis pas a kankr1 que j’a1 d1t ça ! c’est mon pote, ma1s tu sa1s comment 1l n’a1me pas ce vocabula1re...
	      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: ug dis pas ca il va genre se teleporter dans notre conversation avec de la magie fantome juste pour te faire taire
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: oua1s... il te le fais à to1 auss1, hein... c’est complètement fou p*ta1n !
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: ok donc tu as toujours eu des ailes
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: donc je suppose que tes pas secretement tier divin ou quoi
	      @rufioh_talk \nRUFIOH: nan... c’aura1t été cool de part1r à fond sur la roublard1se... hé, peut-être que tu aura1s pu me donner genre, des conse1ls de chapardage... genre en tant que voleuse et tout ! 
	      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: mais nah, je ne pense pas que j'aura1s pu fa1re ça... pas 1ntent1onnellement je veux d1re...
	      @meenah_idle MEENAH: hein pourquoi pas
	      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: je sa1s pas... se su1c1der, c’est... un truc dur à fa1re. je su1s pas comme to1, meenah... je pense pas que tout le monde so1t... enf1n damara est plutôt... mais peut-être que l’on ne devra1t pas entrer dans ce sujet, hahaha. 1l ne faut pas réve1ller le f1duspawn qu1 dort, tu comprends...
	      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: ...
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: ce que je veux d1re c’est que, tu t’es pr1se au jeu... et je peux le comprendre... ma1s je n’a1 jama1s été auss1 courageux que les gens l’ont toujours pensé... je ne sa1s pas pourquo1 1ls pensa1ent toujours ça de mo1. peut-être que ce sont mes a1les ou ma coupe à crète... ou quand je sors des bangarang des fo1s très fort ? ça me fa1t passer pour le type avec beaucoup d’est1me de so1... ma1s mon est1me de mo1 est pas à tomber par terre… j’sa1s pas...
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: daccord tu as pas passe le tier mais je carpe toujours pas un truc
	      @meenah_wut MEENAH: tu avais pas une connerie du genre un putain de corps robot a un moment ou je lai juste imagine
	      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#peut-etre-que-jai-attrape-la-folie-fantome#je-pourrais-JURER-que-tu-etais-un-cheval-de-metal-quand-meme MEENAH: toute cette periode de notre session etait tres embrouillee pour moi probablement parce que jetais morte pendant un bon moment
	      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: oua1111s...
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: non, le  corps robot est vra1ment arr1vé... j’a1 un peu répr1mé ce souven1r auss1, haha... c’éta1t... c’éta1t p*ta1n de quelque chose, yo ! fou...
	      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: je su1s sûr que tu te souv1ens comment tout ça a commencé... quand damara et mo1 sort1ons encore ensemble... ça te d1t quelque chose ?
	      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: ouais
	      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: putain de megido
	      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#taureau#lol#attend...#pourquoi-tu-fais-jamais-de-blague-taurine?#NUL MEENAH: est ce que lon a vraiment besoin dagiter le chiffon rouge
              @rufioh_no \nRUFIOH: non,  non… eh, juste pour d1re c’est tout... c’est toute l’h1sto1re… en tout cas, c’éta1t quand horuss comença1t à fl1rter avec mo1, tu te souv1ens... et je ne voula1s pas vra1ment vac1ller avec lu1 et elle car je sava1s comment elle éta1t… m*rde, s1 jalouse… tellement folle p*ta1n...
	      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: donc elle a fa1t de mo1 un estrop1é tu te souv1ens ?
	      @meenah_idle:#validisme MEENAH: tagge cette merde mon pote
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: p*ta1n, oua1s... je veux d1re, elle m’a tabassé... je pouva1s pas bouger un muscle... enf1n, je pouva1s toujours assez b1en me serv1r de mes a1les, hehe...
	      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: vra1ment, je pensa1s que ça aura1t fa1t l’affa1re, de juste battre mes a1les... je pouva1s toujours voler et juste flotter comme ça, complètement flasque… ça aura1t pu être cool !
	      @rufioh_happytalk:#genre-l1ttéralement...#cette-m*rde-éta1t-tellement-tendue-!#le-mec-est-fort \nRUFIOH: ma1s nan... horuss a pensé à m1eux que ça. 1l a constru1t un corps-robot, c’éta1t tendu...
	      @rufioh_sadtalk:#surtout-sur-les-escal1ers...#}:( \nRUFIOH: ma1s j’a1 perdu mes a1les, ce qu1 cra1nt... et c’éta1t b1zzare d’avo1r juste une vra1e tête sur un grand corps métall1que et de fa1re bouger ces p*ta1n de jambes de la bonne façon, tu sa1s... trotter c’est du trava1l yo.
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: c’est déjà m1eux que d’être un estrop1é. je veux d1re un tétraplég1que, oops, haha... ma1s je suppose que tu ne sa1s pas ce qu1 s’est passé après, vu que to1 et damara vous vous entretu1ez et tout...
	      @meenah_idle MEENAH: non quoi
	      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: et b1en... je su1s mort. oua1s... ma1s...
	      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: c’est genre... wow, une longue h1sto1re... que je suppose tu n’as jama1s entendue... je t’en parlera1 à un autre moment, c’est tout un truc de d1ngue. ma1s...
	      @rufioh_talk:#j'espère-que-quelqu’un-a-pe1nt-cette-m*rde...#chef-d’oeuvre-1nstantané \nRUFIOH: j’éta1s mort, ok ? et horuss m’a embrassé pour me ressusc1ter... ma1s que ma tête je pense... 1l se tena1t probablement sur une quelconque montagne, posant comme un p*ta1n de gangster, probablement en tra1n de se battre contre une bête à sabots avec une cr1n1ère ardente et tout... 
	      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: donc oua1s, après tu m’as vu j’ava1s de nouveau un corps normal... c’éta1t cool de sa part de m’a1der comme 1l l’a fa1t.
	      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: et oua1s, on est sort1t ensemble lu1 et mo1... pendant très longtemps après ça, un peu de temps en temps, même après qu’on so1t morts... au cas où tu alla1s poser la quest1on...
	      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: ca letait pas
	      @rufioh_laugh \nRUFIOH: d’accord... haha... trop d’1nformat1on je suppose ? désolé poupée.
	      @rufioh_talk \nRUFIOH: j’a1 toujours voulu te remerc1er pour m’avo1r toujours défendu... tu sa1s, quand elle m’a estr*p1é... même s1 ça t’a coûté cher… c’éta1t de la pure classe, pe1xes, je l’oubl1era1s jama1s.
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: mec ce serait pas necessaire si tu pouvais juste te defendre toi meme des fois
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: je veux dire malgre etre paralyse
	      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: hé… oua1s... je suppose...
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: tu es le seul mec du groupe qui soit pas loin detre a peu pres cool
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: tout le monde craignait mais tu etais presque bien
	      @meenah_talk MEENAH: sauf que tu as toujours ete une mauviette
	      @meenah_annoyed:#AT#SOUS-ENTENDU-DE-HANDICAP# MEENAH: sans vouloir tinvalider mec
	      @kankri_talk4:#Aussi,-pendant-que-tu-marches,-fais-attenti9n-à-ne-pas-exhi6er-la-santé-de-tes-jam6es. KANKRI: Excuse-m9i. Meenah, "Invalide" est une injure validiste, qui dans ce c9ntexte est VRAIMENT inappr9priée. Tagger tes 6lagues avec des alertes trigger “ir9niques” n’excuse pas cette attitude. Je te remercierais de te réfréner d’utiliser de tels termes dans le futur.
	      @meenah_angry MEENAH: AAAAAUG)(A
	      <!--  -->
	      </args>
		</action>


			<action class='rufiohTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Ask Rufioh to join.'>
			      <args>
			      @meenah_talk MEENAH: i probubbly shouldnt even ask this since youre not as brave as people make out with you to be
			      @meenah_annoyedtalk:#wait#what-did-i-say?#nm MEENAH: i mean make you out to be
			      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: but would you want to come away with me to...
			      @rufioh_notalk \nRUFIOH: whoa, man... not you too!!! ahaha...
			      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: wut
			      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: 1t's f1ne... 1t's alr1ght that you d1g me, 1'm flattered... you were just the last person who hadn't h1t on me yet... and 1 k1nda dug that about you, you know?
			      @meenah_angry MEENAH: i wasnt asking you out dope
			      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: oh... wow... sh*t! sorry, guess 1 got the wrong 1dea...
			      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: 1t's just k1nd of a reflex, doll... you know? everybody h1ts on me all the t1me, and 1 don't know why... sh*t 1s crazy...
			      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: just the other day, get th1s... some orange guy 1n a green sh1rt jumped out of some bushes and tr1ed to k1ss me... and 1'm l1ke whaaat... step off jolly man, haha...
			      @meenah_creepytalk MEENAH: maybe its cause youre a bishie ass glubberfucker with a kickin hawk
			      @rufioh_happytalk:#1-could-g1ve-you-mohawk-dy1ng-t1ps...#you'd-rock-the-sh*t-out-of-that-look!!! \nRUFIOH: yo, that's cool of you to say...  you've got k1nda th1s otenba b1shojo th1ng go1ng on yourself, g1rl... your style rocks, 1 always thought you looked pretty slamm1n...
			      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: for what its worth
			      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: i would be your moe dere dere waifu in the beat of a pump biscuit
			      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: if i was remotely attracted to you or found your personality more appealing
			      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: and also if i shared your dumb passion for troll anime and didnt think it clogged massive blowhole
			      @rufioh_talk \nRUFIOH: ahaha, bangarang! that's a scenar1o 1'd be alr1ght w1th...
			      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: no one really to talk to anymore about my stor1es, yo... s1nce th1ngs got so ch1lly w1th my ex...
			      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: goddamn witch
			      @rufioh_offended \nRUFIOH: seriously... she crazy...
			      @rufioh_happytalk:#and-1f-not-what-brand-of-mohawk-dye-1-use? \nRUFIOH: so what were you go1ng to ask me... uh, 1f not on a date?
			      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: never mind
			      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: youre not even gonna agree anyway cause this team suuuuucks
			      @meenah_happy MEENAH: later ruf
			      <!--  -->
			      </args>
			</action>


			<action class='rufiohTalk3' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Be Rufioh.'>
			      <args>
			      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: oh sh*t... you want to be me? ok that's pretty dope 1 guess.
			      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: but can 1t wa1t? my lusus 1s m1ss1ng aga1n and 1 can't th1nk stra1ght w1thout h1m... he's my happy thought!!! haha...
			      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: 1 hope damara d1dn't do someth1ng w1th h1m... she l1kes to f*** w1th me somet1mes by stash1ng the l1ttle guy somewhere... she's bonkers!!!
			      <!--  -->
			      </args>
			</action>

<action class='rufiohTalk4' sprite='horuss' command='talk' name='Talk to Rufioh.'>
      <args>
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: hey man. oh, heh... st1ll mak1ng that face 1 see... 
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Yes, I really enjoy making this face. It really helps remind me through persistent facial discomfort that appearing to be happy should always be one's top priority.
      @horuss_oops HORUSS: 8=O &lt; Why? You don't find it displeasing, do you?
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: um... no... 1t's uh... yeah, 1t's alr1ght horuss. the look 1s really, uh... someth1ng else. wow.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Really, I could stop making the face. Meenah recently ordered me to stop making it in her presence, and I of course instantly complied. I would just as readily do the same for someone as important to me as you.
      @rufioh_sheepish:#except-for-maybe#po1nt1ng-1t-at-me-so-much... \nRUFIOH: err... haha. that's cool... but yeah, that's f1ne. really 1 can d1g the look, 1 guess. just do whatever you're feel1ng w1th 1t...
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Rufioh, your affable malleability continues to be your finest quality. It is the jewel in your mohawk. A true diamond in the Ruf. You always were the ideal embodiment of your aspect, as pleasantly wayward and fickle as The Breeze itself.
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: yeah... uh... thanks. 1 should probably try to work on that though...
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Of course. We always strive to hone our craft, ever pounding at the iron to make the shoe a perfect shape. I know well how much work it takes.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: no, 1 d1dn't mean, l1ke... be MORE l1ke that... 1 mean... uh, sorry to 1nterrupt... go ahead?
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; My path was similarly governed by my aspect. For the longest time, I felt as if I was a blank sheet of paper. Like I had to make myself out of nothing.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And so I began to listen closely to the void within myself and corral the various personal attributes I herd calling to me. 
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Much like assembling a comple%25 machine, I began to piece together a STRONG identity, which of course included discovering a passion for mechani%25 itself.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And needless to say, what also galloped out of the void in my soul was the realization that I am obviously a noble hoofbeast, though my physical appearance cruelly betrays this fact.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: hey, uh... horuss... 1 th1nk...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: we need to talk.
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: 1 mean, when you get a m1nute...
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; And in following sweeps I would keep turning my mechanically augmented, acute equine ear back to the abyss within, and continue to discover more about myself. I would learn that I was more complicated than I ever imagined. More complicated than any mortal mind could understand a person to be.
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Knowing myself to be hoofbeastkin was only grazing the surface of the pasture. Merely skimming the cream from the top of the milk. I was so much more.
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: 1 th1nk maybe we should l1ke...
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: uh... see other...
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; It turns out my body was merely the host to a highly intricate system of entities of any sort you could name, biological or mechanical, sentient or nonsentient, physical or metaphysical. My inner field of e%25perience is shared by the souls of ancient legendary musclebeasts, a range of devices such as hivehold appliances, a number of cosmological features such as planets, star systems, even several universes, and a variety of abstract concepts which sentient beings have not yet formed the language to e%25press.
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: l1ke... don't get me wrong... we had some good t1mes together... 1t's been great really...
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: but maybe 1t's t1me to uh... 1 dunno.
      @horuss_crossed HORUSS: 8=D &lt; But as much as I learned about myself, I could never find a way to become whole.
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; The void was never filled until you came along, Rufioh. 
      @rufioh_surprise \nRUFIOH: wow man. that's...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: wow.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; If there is any lesson I would like people to take from my story, it is a lesson that is a multiple system consisting of two distinct lessons.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; The first is how love heals all wounds, even ones consisting of the infinite essence of void permeating your entire e%25istence and role as a legendary hero.
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; The second is how if you are faced with any crisis of identity whatsoever, it's really important to do your best to manufacture esoteric features of your personality and believe in them very STRONGLY and tell people about those things as frequently as possible.
      @horuss_bashful HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I can assure you right now, the labor involved in smithing my personality into one that is interesting and complicated was rather intensive.
      @horuss_sweat_bashful2 HORUSS: 8=D~~ &lt; I really worked up a good sweat in the process.
      @horuss_sweat_bashful HORUSS: 8=D~~~~ &lt; (That is the sweat dripping from my face.)
      @rufioh_no \nRUFIOH: hey... yo... that...
      @rufioh_no \nRUFIOH: that's some freaky sh*t dog!
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Anyway, I apologize for talking so much. You know how you have a way of drawing the breath out of people.
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; What were you trying to tell me?
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: oh... yeah.
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: uh...
      @rufioh_sad \nRUFIOH: never m1nd.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
<action class='rufiohTalk5' sprite='damara' command='talk' name='Talk to Rufioh.'>
      <args>
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: gotta be honest damara... 1 been feel1ng pretty bad...
      @damara_huh DAMARA: なぜですか？
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: um... you can keep a secret, r1ght?
      @damara_fiendish DAMARA: はい、もちろん。私はあなたの友達です。
      @rufioh_surprise \nRUFIOH: yeah...
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: 1t's horuss... and you know... been th1nk1ng about break1ng 1t off w1th h1m...
      @damara_talk DAMARA: 何を壊す？彼のホーン？
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: hahaha! naw... that wouldn't do much good...
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: 1 mean... 1 feel l1ke a chump for even th1nk1ng about 1t... he's been so cool...
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: but d*mn! etern1ty 1s a long f***1ng t1me!!! 1 dunno 1f a relat1onsh1p should really last that long...
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたのセックスライフはどうですか？
      @rufioh_notalk \nRUFIOH: whoa, uh... k1nda personal quest1on? anyway that's not 1t... 
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: 1 feel gu1lty for say1ng so... 1'm just not 1nto 1t... so many repet1t1ve dates over the m1llen1a... so much l1ke... talk1ng about l1vestock and b1g muscular an1mals and... 1 dunno. those aren't really my 1nterests...
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: maybe we were never that compat1ble and 1 just never had the guts to say so?
      @damara_sadtalk DAMARA: RUFIOH。私はあなたにこのことを告げた。毎日。永遠に。
      @rufioh_laugh \nRUFIOH: 1 know, 1 know... 1 d1dn't l1sten to you... 1 f1gured you were st1ll all mad and jealous!!!
      @damara_mean DAMARA: 私は怒って嫉妬した。
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: r1ght... 1 just don't know what to do.
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: he's great... but he's so cl1ngy! 1 don't know how he keeps that up after all th1s t1me... dude's got stam1na... 1'm just l1ke... romant1cally exhausted. you get me, doll?
      @damara_meantalk DAMARA: はい。愛が私には死んでいる。ので、誰かがずっと前に、心臓を介して私を刺した。
      @rufioh_idle \nRUFIOH: heh, touche.
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: but for real... 1 just don't want to hurt h1s feel1ngs...
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: あなたは私が彼を殺したいですか？再び？
      @rufioh_notalk \nRUFIOH: no!!! god, no... don't hurt anyone... let's not go there aga1n!
      @damara_smile DAMARA: 私が彼を誘惑したいですか？
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: er... 1 guess 1f the two of you are l1ke... um. that's really between you and h1m? not sure he would go for that... anyway, 1 don't th1nk that would actually help me...
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: 私は彼の魂を消費するために悪魔をもたらすでしょう。
      @rufioh_notalk \nRUFIOH: man, no! 1 told you, please don't feed anyone's soul to ANYBODY!!!
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: you've got to keep crazy talk l1ke that down, damara!
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: 1f people knew some of the sh*t you sa1d... how you say crazy sh*t l1ke you want to serve h1m... f***!
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: 1t wouldn't be cool... people would fl1p...
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: h*ll, d1dn't you hear meenah was try1ng to ra1se an army to k1ll h1m?
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: 1f she could hear some of the th1ngs you told me... sh*t... 1 can't ever let her f1nd out...
      @rufioh_sad:#}:( \nRUFIOH: 1f she knew, you'd both start f1ght1ng aga1n...
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは必然だけを遅らせる。
      @damara_squint DAMARA: 私たちの終了時間が近いです。
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
    </classes>
</sburb>
